♪ I'M GOING DOWN
TO SOUTH PARK ♪
♪ GONNA HAVE MYSELF
A TIME ♪
♪ FRIENDLY FACES
EVERYWHERE ♪
♪ HUMBLE FOLKS
WITHOUT TEMPTATION ♪
♪ GOING DOWN
TO SOUTH PARK ♪
♪ GONNA LEAVE
MY WOE'S BEHIND ♪
♪ AMPLE PARKING
DAY OR NIGHT ♪
♪ PEOPLE SPOUTING,
"HOWDY NEIGHBOR" ♪
♪ HEADED ON
UP TO SOUTH PARK ♪
♪ GONNA SEE IF
I CAN'T UNWIND ♪
( mumbling )
♪ SO COME ON DOWN
TO SOUTH PARK ♪
♪ AND MEET SOME
FRIENDS OF MINE ♪
♪ SCHOOL DAYS,
SCHOOL DAYS ♪
♪ TEACHER... ♪
MY LITTLE BROTHER'S
TRYING TO FOLLOW ME
TO SCHOOL AGAIN.
IKE, YOU CAN'T COME
TO SCHOOL WITH ME !
YEAH, GO HOME,
YOU LITTLE DILDO !
DUDE DON'T CALL
MY BROTHER A DILDO !
WHAT'S A DILDO ?
I DON'T KNOW.
AND I'LL BET CARTMAN
DOESN'T KNOW EITHER.
I KNOW
WHAT IT MEANS !
WELL, WHAT ?
I'M NOT
TELLING YOU.
WHAT'S A DILDO
KENNY ?
( mumbling )
THAT'S WHAT KYLE'S LITTLE
BROTHER IS ALRIGHT.
DUDE, THAT
KICKS ASS !
YEAH, CHECK
THIS ONE OUT !
READY IKE,
KICK THE BABY.
DON'T KICK
THE BABY.
KICK THE BABY.
AHH...
WHOA CARTMAN,
LOOKS LIKE YOU DIDN'T
GET MUCH SLEEP LAST NIGHT.
THAT'S BECAUSE I WAS HAVING
THESE BOGUS NIGHTMARES.
REALLY,
WHAT ABOUT ?
WELL, I DREAMT THAT
I WAS LYING IN MY BED,
IN THE DARK.
WHEN ALL OF A SUDDEN
THIS BRIGHT BLUE LIGHT
FILLED THE ROOM.
AND SLOWLY MY BEDROOM
DOOR BEGAN TO OPEN.
AND THEN THE NEXT THING
I REMEMBER,
I WAS BEING DRAGGED
THROUGH A HALLWAY.
THEN I WAS LYING
ON A TABLE,
AND THESE SCARY ALIENS
WANTED TO OPERATE ON ME.
AND THEY HAD BIG HEADS
AND BIG BLACK EYES.
DUDE,
TOTALLY !      VISITORS !
WHAT ?
THAT WASN'T
A DREAM CARTMAN,
THOSE WERE
VISITORS !
NO, IT WAS
JUST A DREAM,
MY MOM SAID SO.
VISITORS
ARE REAL.
THEY ABDUCT PEOPLE
AND THEY MUTILATE COWS.
SHUT UP YOU GUYS,
YOU'RE JUST TRYING
TO MAKE ME SCARED.
AND IT'S NOT WORKING.
HELLO THERE
CHILDREN.
HEY CHEF.
WHAT'S GONNA BE FOR
LUNCH TODAY CHEF ?
TODAY IT'S
SALISBURY STEAK
WITH BUTTERED NOODLES.
AND A CHOICE OF
GREEN BEAN CASSEROLE
OR VEGETABLE
MEDLEY.
KICK ASS.
DID ANY
OF YOU CHILDREN
SEE THE ALIEN SPACESHIP
LAST NIGHT ?
YEAH, FAT BOY
SAW IT.
NO, THAT WAS
JUST A DREAM.
AND I'M NOT FAT
I'M BIG BONED !
WAS IT THE ONES
WITH THE BIG LONG HEADS
AND THE BLACK
EYES ?
OH !
THEY TOOK HIM
ON THEIR SHIP.
OH, DID THEY GIVE YOU
AN ANAL PROBE ?
WHAT'S AN
ANAL PROBE ?
THAT'S WHEN THEY PUT
THIS BIG METAL HOOP-A-JOOP
UP YOUR BUTT.
WHOA, THEY GAVE YOU
AN ANAL PROBE CARTMAN ?
NO, I MEAN...
WHY WOULD THEY DO THAT ?
DUDE THEY DID, HUH ?
ALIENS STUCK
STUFF UP YOUR ASS !
NO !
ANAL PROBE.
SHUT UP DILDO !
WELL, I GOT TO
GET TO THE CAFETERIA.
YOU CHILDREN WATCH
THAT FAT BOY NOW,
HE CAN BE UNDER
ALIEN CONTROL.
WE TOLD YOU THEY
WERE REAL, CARTMAN.
SORRY TO HEAR
ABOUT YOUR ASS.
GODAMMIT, THEY DIDN'T
DO ANYTHING TO MY ASS !
IT WAS JUST
A DREAM !
WHY YOU WALKING
SO FUNNY CARTMAN ?
SHUT UP !
NO IKE, GO HOME.
THIS IS IT,
THIS ONE'S
FOR THE GAME.
KICK THE BABY.
GOOD MORNING
MISS CRABTREE.
SIT DOWN, WE'RE
RUNNING LATE !
DAMMIT,
HE'S STILL THERE.
DON'T WORRY
ABOUT HIM.
NO DUDE,
IF SOMETHING
HAPPENS TO HIM,
MY PARENTS ARE
GONNA BLAME ME.
SIT DOWN
BACK THERE !
AHH !
YEAH WHATEVER,
YOU FAT BITCH.
WHAT DID
YOU SAY ?!
I SAID I HAVE
A BAD ITCH.
OH !
OH MY GOD !
VISITORS.
( mumbling )
IKE !
STOP THE BUS !
MISS CRABTREE, YOU HAVE
TO STOP THIS BUS !
DO YOU WANT AN
OFFICE REFERRAL ?
NO.
THEN SIT DOWN !
BUT I...
AHH !
AH !
CARTMAN, ARE THOSE
THE SAME VISITORS YOU SAW ?
SHUT UP YOU GUYS,
IT'S NOT WORKING.
WE HAVE TO
DO SOMETHING.
WE CAN'T DO
ANYTHING FOR NOW
THAT FAT BITCH
WON'T LET US.
WHAT DID YOU SAY ?
I SAID THAT
RABBITS EAT LETTUCE.
WELL YES,
THEY CERTAINLY DO.
WHAT AM I
GONNA DO ?
MY LITTLE BROTHER HAS
BEEN ABDUCTED BY ALIENS.
( farting )
YOU FARTED.
SOMEBODY IS
BAKING BROWNIES.
THAT'S THE THIRD COW
THIS MONTH.
AT THIS RATE,
ALL MY CATTLE ARE GONNA DIE
BEFORE THE WINTER'S THROUGH.
THIS IS NOTHING
OUT OF THE UNUSUAL.
COWS TURN THEMSELVES
INSIDE OUT ALL THE TIME.
PEOPLE BEEN SAYING
THEY'VE BEEN SEEING
UFO'S AROUND.
UFO'S ?
YEAH, AND BLACK ARMY
CIA HELICOPTERS AND TRUCKS.
THAT'S THE SILLIEST
THING I'VE EVER HEARD.
WHAT WAS THAT ?
THAT WAS
A PIGEON.
WHAT AM I
SUPPOSED TO DO ?
JUST STAND HERE
AND WATCH MY COWS
GET MUTILATED
ONE BY ONE ?
( whistling )
HEY, MY CATTLE !
YOU SEE ?
THERE IS SOMETHING
FUNNY GOING ON.
THERE'S NOTHING
I'LL GET
THOSE COWS BACK.
AND NOW CHILDREN,
OUR FRIEND MR. HAT
IS GOING TO TELL US
ABOUT CHRISTOPHER COLUMBUS.
THAT'S RIGHT
MR. GARRISON,
CHRISTOPHER COLUMBUS
DISCOVERED AMERICA,
AND WAS THE INDIAN'S
BEST FRIEND.
HE HELPED THE INDIANS
WIN THEIR WAR AGAINST
FREDERICK DOUGLAS,
AND FREED THE HEBREWS
FROM NAPOLEON.
AND DISCOVERED FRANCE.
I CAN'T
JUST SIT HERE.
I HAVE TO HELP
MY STUPID BROTHER.
I'LL COME HOME
WITHOUT HIM
AND MY DAD WILL
START YELLING.
"WHERE'S YOUR
BROTHER, KYLE !?"
"YOU WEREN'T LOOKING OUT FOR
YOUR LITTLE BROTHER, KYLE."
OKAY, LET'S DITCH
SCHOOL AND GO FIND HIM.
"YOU KNOW HE CAN'T THINK
ON HIS OWN, KYLE."
"BRUSH AND FLOSS, KYLE."
"WHERE HAS THAT
FINGER BEEN, KYLE ?"
DUDE !
IS THERE A
PROBLEM BOYS ?
YES MR. GARRISON,
I HAVE TO GO NOW.
OH REALLY, KYLE.
WHAT IS IT THIS TIME,
ANOTHER PROSTATE TUMOR ?
NO, MY LITTLE BROTHER'S
BEEN ABDUCTED BY ALIENS.
IT'S TRUE,
ASK CARTMAN.
THEY GAVE HIM
AN ANAL PROBE.
THAT'S A
LITTLE JOKE.
MR. GARRISON,
SERIOUSLY, I HAVE TO GO.
CAN I PLEASE BE
EXCUSED FROM CLASS ?
I DON'T KNOW KYLE,
DID YOU ASK MR. HAT ?
I DON'T WANT
TO ASK MR. HAT.
I'M ASKING YOU !
I THINK YOU SHOULD
ASK MR. HAT.
MR. HAT, MAY I PLEASE
BE EXCUSED FROM CLASS ?
WELL KYLE, NO !
YOU HEAR ME ?
YOU GO TO HELL !
YOU GO TO HELL
AND YOU DIE !
I GUESS YOU'LL HAVE TO
TAKE YOUR SEAT.
DAMMIT !
HA, HA, MR. HAT
YELLED AT YOU.
OW, MY ASS !
DAMN CARTMAN.
DUDE, HE'S
FARTING FIRE.
IT'S THE ALIEN
ANAL PROBE !
IT'S SHOOTING FIRE FROM
CARTMAN'S RECTUM !
THAT WAS JUST
A DREAM.
ERIC, DO YOU NEED TO
SIT IN THE CORNER
UNTIL YOUR FLAMING
GAS IS UNDER CONTROL ?
NO MR. GARRISON,
I'M FINE.
OWW !
HEY, YOU COWS CAN'T
GET ON THIS TRAIN.
THIS IS A
PEOPLE TRAIN.
YOU COWS HAVE NO BUSINESS
ON A PEOPLE TRAIN, ALRIGHT ?
'CAUSE YOU'RE COWS.
NO, NO, NO.
DON'T TRY ANY OF THAT COW
HYPNOSIS ON ME, ALRIGHT ?
'CAUSE IT'S
NOT GONNA WORK.
HOLD IT RIGHT
THERE COWS.
COME BACK HERE !
( chatter )
AHH !
I SURE AM HUNGRY.
HOW CAN YOU EAT WHEN
YOU'RE FARTING FIRE ?
SHUT UP DUDE, YOU'RE
BEING TOTALLY IMMATURE.
HEY LOOK, THERE'S
WENDY TESTABERGER.
WHERE ?
( romantic music )
♪ STAN WANTS TO KISS,
WENDY TESTABERGER ♪
SHUT UP FAT ASS,
I DON'T EVEN LIKE HER !
I'M NOT FAT AND
YOU OBVIOUSLY LIKE HER
BECAUSE YOU THROW UP
EVERY TIME SHE TALKS TO YOU.
I DO NOT.
HI, GUYS.
HI, WENDY.
HERE STAN,
THIS IS FOR YOU.
EWW !
BYE,      BYE,
WENDY.    WENDY.
DUDE, WHAT DOES
THE NOTE SAY ?
HOLY CRAP,
IT SAYS SHE WANTS TO
MEET ME AT STARK'S POND
AFTER SCHOOL.
WHOA, MAYBE
YOU CAN KISS HER.
OR SLIP HER THE TONGUE.
( mumbling )
WHAT, HOW DO YOU
KNOW SHE HAS A CAT ?
COME ON YOU GUYS,
WE NEED TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO GET OUT OF SCHOOL
SO WE CAN GET MY
LITTLE BROTHER BACK.
HELLO THERE
CHILDREN.
HEY CHEF.
HOW ARE
YOU DOING ?            BAD.
WHY BAD ?
CHEF, HAVE YOU EVER HAD
SOMETHING HAPPEN TO YOU
BUT NOBODY
BELIEVED YOU ?
OH CHILDREN,
CHILDREN.
THAT'S A PROBLEM
WE'VE ALL HAD TO FACE
AT SOME TIME
OR ANOTHER.
HERE, LET ME SING
YOU A LITTLE SONG.
IT MIGHT
CLEAR THINGS UP.
♪ I'M GONNA MAKE LOVE
TO YOU WOMAN ♪
♪ GONNA LAY YOU DOWN
BY THE FIRE ♪
♪ AND CARESS YOUR
WOMANLY BODY ♪
♪ MAKE YOU MOAN
AND PERSPIRE ♪
♪ GONNA GET THOSE
JUICES FLOWING ♪
♪ WE'RE MAKING
LOVE, BABY ♪
♪ LOVE BABY,
LOVE, LOVE, BABY... ♪
CHEF !
HUH ?!
DO YOU FEEL BETTER ?
NO.
OH CHILDREN,
WHAT CAN BE SO BAD ?
IT'S SALISBURY
STEAK DAY.
VISITORS TOOK
KYLE'S BABY BROTHER.
WHAT ?!
WHAT THE HELL DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE DOING
IN SCHOOL EATING
SALISBURY STEAK ?
GO FIND HIM,
DAMMIT !
MR. GARRISON WON'T
LET US OUT OF SCHOOL.
HE THINKS WE'RE
MAKING IT UP.
YOU ARE
MAKING IT UP !
WHOA.
WHAT ?
THAT WAS COOL.
IT'S SOME KIND OF
SYMBIONIC METAMORPHOSE DEVICE.
THIS CAN MEAN THE VISITORS
WANT TO COMMUNICATE WITH US.
OH I SEE.
NOW YOU'RE GONNA JOIN IN
ON THE LITTLE JOKE.
IT'S NO JOKE CHILDREN,
THIS IS BIG.
PLEASE CHEF, IF I DON'T
GET OUT OF SCHOOL
AND GET MY BROTHER BACK
FROM THE ALIENS,
MY PARENTS ARE
GONNA DISOWN ME.
HOLD ON,
HOLD ON NOW.
YOU GOT TO
HELP THE CHILDREN.
HEY, YOU GUYS SURE
ARE GOING A LONG WAY
TO TRY AND
SCARE ME.
I WANT MY
SALISBURY STEAK.
FIRE DRILL,
FIRE DRILL !
EVERYBODY OUT !
OKAY CHILDREN,
THIS IS YOUR CHANCE.
KILLER,
THANKS CHEF.
MAN, OH MAN.
FIRST CONTACT WITH
THE ALIEN VISITORS !
I'VE GOT TO
GET MYSELF READY.
♪ WE GOT OUT
OF SCHOOL ♪
♪ NO MORE
SCHOOL TODAY ♪
♪ WE GOT OUT
OF SCHOOL... ♪
OH, YOU GUYS MY ASS,
SERIOUSLY !!
OKAY CARTMAN
YOU CAN STOP
FARTING FIRE NOW.
I WOULD IF I COULD
YOU SON-OF-A-BITCH !
SO HOW DO WE GET
MY LITTLE BROTHER BACK ?
WOULD YOU STOP GOING ON
ABOUT YOUR LITTLE BROTHER ?!
I KNOW IT WAS
JUST A DREAM !
I KNOW I DIDN'T
HAVE AN ANAL PROBE !
AND I KNOW THAT I'M
NOT UNDER ALIEN CONTROL !
♪ I LOVE TO SINGA ♪
♪ ABOUT THE MOONA
AND THE JUNA AND THE SPRINGA ♪
♪ I LOVE TO SINGA ♪
♪ ABOUT A SKY OF BLUE
OR TEA FOR TWO...♪
WHAT THE HELL
WAS THAT ?!
HE IS UNDER
ALIEN CONTROL.
THAT THING
IN HIS BUTT
IS LINKED UP TO
THE VISITORS !
SON-OF-A-BITCH !
YOU GUYS SHUT UP,
I'M NOT UNDER
ALIEN CONTROL !
HEY, IF YOU VISITORS
CAN HEAR ME,
BRING ME BACK
MY LITTLE BROTHER,
GODAMMIT !
THAT HURTS
YOU BUTT LICKER !
KYLE LOOK,
IT'S THEM.
GIVE ME BACK
MY BROTHER !
OH MY GOD,
THEY KILLED KENNY !
YOU BASTARDS,
COME BACK HERE !
COME BACK !
DAMMIT, WE
WERE SO CLOSE !
HEY LOOK, I THINK
KENNY'S OKAY.
( mumbling )
OH !
( sirens )
WOW, POOR KENNY.
NOW DO YOU
BELIEVE US
CARTMAN ?
NO.
CARTMAN, THEY
KILLED KENNY !
HE'S NOT DEAD.
DUDE, KENNY
IS DEAD.
SEE ?
SHUT UP
YOU GUYS.
HE'S DEAD
CARTMAN !
GODAMMIT, I DIDN'T
HAVE AN ANAL PROBE !
SCREW YOU GUYS,
I'M GOING HOME !
GO ON AND GO HOME
YOU FAT CHICKEN !
DILDO !
YOU'RE ALL
I HAVE LEFT, STAN.
SORRY DUDE, I GOTTA
GO MEET WENDY.
YOU CAN'T.
POOR IKE MUST
BE SO SCARED.
UP THERE
ALL ALONE.
YOU GOTTA
HELP ME DUDE.
DUDE, LIKE
CHEF SAYS,
I GOTTA GET
A PIECE OF LOVING
WHILE THE
GETTING'S HOT.
RATS !
HELLO ERIC.
HI MOM.
HOW ARE YOU
DOING ?
WELL, I'M
PISSED OFF
HERE, I MADE YOU POWDERED
DONUT PANCAKE SURPRISE.
I DON'T WANT POWDERED
DONUT PANCAKE SURPRISE !
ALL THE KIDS IN SCHOOL
CALL ME FAT.
YOU'RE NOT FAT,
YOU'RE BIG BONED.
THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
YOU CAN HAVE AN
EENSY-WEENSY BIT,
CAN'T YOU ?
NO !
JUST A WEENSY-EENSY
WOO-WOO ?
NO, LEAVE ME
ALONE MOM !
HOW ABOUT A NICE CHOCOLATE
CHICKEN POT PIE THEN ?
WELL, THAT SOUNDS
PRETTY GOOD.
MOM ?
YES HON ?
IF ANYBODY CALLS
OR COMES OVER,
I'M NOT HERE, OKAY ?
SURE, HON.
YOU WANT SOME
CHEESY POOFS TOO ?
YEAH, I WANT
CHEESY POOFS.
WELL, LOOKS LIKE
SHE'S NOT GONNA
SHOW UP STAN.
LET'S GO LOOK FOR
THE VISITORS NOW.
BUT HER NOTE SAID
SHE'D BE HERE.
HI, STAN.
EW.
YOU CAN'T TALK
TO STAN, WENDY,
HE THROWS UP
WHEN YOU DO.
BUT WHY STAN ?
EW.
COULD YOU GUYS
JUST GET DOWN
TO BUSINESS
SO WE CAN FIND
MY LITTLE BROTHER ?
HUH ?
JUST MAKE SWEET LOVE
DOWN BY THE FIRE.
WHAT HAPPENED TO
YOUR LITTLE BROTHER ?
As the reports of
UFO sightings increase,
more mysterious crop circle
patters are appearing
in fields all around
South Park.
These crop circles
when viewed from above,
form strange patterns.
HEY, THAT KIND OF
LOOKS LIKE,
TOM SELLECK.
Could it be that
aliens are trying to
make contact with us,
here on earth ?
MEOW.
NO KITTY, THIS
IS MY POT PIE !
MEOW.
NO, BAD KITTY.
NO KITTY, THIS
IS MY POT PIE !
MOM, KITTY'S
BEING A DILDO !
WELL THEN I KNOW
A CERTAIN KITTY KITTY
WHO'S SLEEPING
WITH MOMMY TONIGHT.
WHAT ?!
AND NOW I HAVE TO GO
HOME WITHOUT HIM
AND MY PARENTS ARE
GONNA HAVE ME KILLED !
WHY DIDN'T YOU GO
GET THE FAT KID ?
WHY ?
IF THE FAT KID HAS SOMETHING
IMPLANTED IN HIS ASS,
MAYBE THE VISITORS
ARE USING HIM
AS PART OF
THEIR PLAN.
YOU SHOULD USE
THE FAT KID AS BAIT
TO BRING THEM BACK.
HEY, YOU'RE
RIGHT WENDY.
COME ON STAN, WE HAVE
TO GO GET CARTMAN.
COME ON STAN.
EW !
HEY WAIT.
WHEN DO I GET TO
MAKE SWEET LOVE ?
MEOW.
NO KITTY, YOU
CAN'T HAVE ANY !
MEOW.
NO KITTY, THIS
IS MY POT PIE !
BAD KITTY.
EXCUSE ME KITTY.
ERIC, LOOK
WHO'S HERE.
GOOD GRIEF MOM !
COME ON, WE'RE GONNA
PLAY AT THE BUS STOP.
I CAN'T,
MY MOM SAYS...
THAT'S OKAY ERIC,
I THINK YOU
NEED TO SPEND TIME
WITH YOUR
LITTLE FRIENDS.
But mom, I don't
want to spend time...
DON'T BE
DIFFICULT ERIC !
NOW YOU GO OUT AND
PLAY IN THE FUN SNOW.
GODAMMIT !
YOU GUYS, I HAVE
TO GET HOME.
DON'T BE SUCH A
FRAIDY CAT CARTMAN.
THIS ROPE
WILL MAKE SURE
THEY CAN'T TAKE YOU
ON BOARD AGAIN.
MAN, THIS SUCKS !
HOW COME THE VISITORS
AREN'T COMING FOR HIM ?
I THINK WE HAVE
TO SIGNAL THEM SOMEHOW.
OWW !
HEY, HE'S
LIKE RUDOLPH.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS
FART SOME MORE CARTMAN
AND THE VISITORS
ARE SURE TO COME.
REALLY ?!
I DON'T THINK I HAVE
TO FART ANYMORE TONIGHT.
SURE YOU DO.
COME ON
CARTMAN, FART !
I DON'T WANNA !
HE CAN'T HOLD
IT IN FOREVER.
FART, DAMN YOU !
OKAY, THAT
DOES IT !
NOW LISTEN,
WHY IS IT THAT
EVERYTHING TODAY
HAS INVOLVED THINGS
EITHER GOING IN
OR COMING OUT
OF MY ASS ?!
I'M SICK OF IT !
IT'S COMPLETELY
IMMATURE !
HEY, IT'S
HAPPENING AGAIN.
WHOA, LOOK AT THAT.
NOW DO YOU
BELIEVE US CARTMAN ?
YOU GUYS
CAN'T SCARE ME.
I KNOW YOU'RE
MAKING IT ALL UP.
THERE'S AN 80 FOOT
SATELLITE DISH
STICKING OUT
OF YOUR ASS !
SURE YOU GUYS,
WHATEVER.
OH BOY,
THE ALIENS ARE GOING
TO MAKE FIRST CONTACT.
HEY, DOWN HERE !
WE ARE READY
FOR YOUR WISDOM.
AND YOU ONLY
GOT 20 MINUTES
BEFORE
"SANFORD AND SON"
IS ON !
YOU GUYS,
I AM SERIOUSLY
GETTING PISSED
OFF RIGHT NOW.
I KNOW THERE'S NO SUCH
THING AS ALIENS !
GODAMMIT !
I TELL YOU,
THERE'S CRAZY STUFF
GOING ON IN THIS TOWN.
YOU CAN SAY THAT
AGAIN MR. GARRISON.
COME DOWN HERE
YOU STINKING ALIENS !
UH, UH...
GO ON KYLE,
ASK THEM FOR YOUR
LITTLE BROTHER BACK.
VISITORS,
THIS MORNING YOU
TOOK MY BROTHER IKE.
HE'S THE LITTLE
FRECKLED KID
THAT LOOKS LIKE
A FOOTBALL.
AT FIRST I WAS HAPPY
YOU TOOK HIM AWAY.
BUT I'VE LEARNED
SOMETHING TODAY.
THAT HAVING
A LITTLE BROTHER
IS A PRETTY
SPECIAL THING.
HECK MR. VISITORS,
I'M JUST A KID ALL ALONE
IN THIS CRAZY WORLD.
BUT IF YOU CAN FIND IT
IN YOUR HEARTS
OR WHATEVER YOU HAVE
TO GIVE MY BROTHER
BACK TO ME,
IT SURE WOULD MAKE
MY LIFE BRIGHTER AGAIN.
THAT WAS
BEAUTIFUL DUDE.
DID IT WORK ?
NOPE, THEY'RE
LEAVING.
HEY YOU SCRAWNY
ASSED %$#@!...
WHAT THE %$& IS
WRONG WITH YOU ?
YOU MUST BE
SOME KIND OF &%$#@
TO BE ABLE TO IGNORE
A CRYING CHILD !
WHOA, DUDE !
YOU KNOW WHAT
YOU &%$#@ LIKE ?
YOU LIKE TO
%$#@&$...
( beeped out )
HEY WENDY,
WHAT'S A &%$#@ ?
IKE, JUMP DOWN, NOW !
FOR THE LOVE
OF GOD IKE, JUMP !
DON'T HURT ME...
( mooing )
MOO.
COME ON IKE,
I PROMISE I'LL BE NICE
TO YOU FROM NOW ON.
DON'T KICK
THE BABY.
WHAT THE HELL ARE
THEY TALKING ABOUT ?
IKE !
DO YOUR IMPERSONATION OF
DAVID CARUSO'S CAREER.
IT'S MY TURN.
YOU GUYS GET ME
DOWN FROM HERE.
HELP !
HELP... !
DILDO !!
I'M SURE GLAD
THAT'S OVER WITH.
YEAH, BOY, AM I
GLAD TO SEE YOU IKE.
FLY IN THE SKY.
WAIT !
WHERE ARE YOU GOING
ALIEN VISITORS ?
COME BACK !
WELL CHEF, WHERE'S
THIS AMAZING THING
YOU WERE GONNA
SHOW US ?
WELL, IT'S IN
THE BEDROOM, LADIES.
COME ON IN.
COME ON IKE,
WE CAN MAKE IT IN
TIME FOR DINNER.
THANKS FOR YOUR
HELP WENDY.
WHATEVER DUDE.
HEY, I DIDN'T
THROW UP !
COOL.
( romantic music )
EW !
SORRY.
HEY LOOK,
A FRENCH FRY.
COOL.
AND WHAT IS THAT ?
I THINK IT'S PART
OF A CHEESY POOF.
HEY, WHAT'S THAT ?
THAT'S A HAMBURGER.
THAT'S FROM LIKE
TWO DAYS AGO.
HEY, WHAT
ABOUT THAT ?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
THE HELL THAT IS !
AND CARTMAN STILL
ISN'T AROUND.
YEAH, WE'RE RUNNING
OUT OF FRIENDS.
I WONDER WHAT
THAT THING WAS
THAT THE VISITORS
GAVE THE COWS ?
COWS, I GOT
YOU CORNERED.
LET'S SEE YOU
GET AWAY NOW.
♪ I LOVE TO SINGA ♪
♪ ABOUT THE MOONA
AND THE JUNA AND THE SPRINGA ♪
♪ I LOVE TO SINGA ♪
♪ ABOUT A SKY OF BLUE
OR TEA FOR TWO...♪
OH, HEY CARTMAN.
WOW CARTMAN.
THE VISITORS
DROPPED YOU OFF
JUST IN TIME
TO GO TO SCHOOL.
OH MAN,
I HAD THIS CRAZY
NIGHTMARE LAST NIGHT.
REALLY,
WHAT ABOUT ?
WELL I WAS STANDING
OUT IN A FIELD
AND I HAD THIS HUGE
SATELLITE DISH
STICKING OUT
OF MY BUTT.
AND THEN THERE WAS
HUNDREDS OF COWS AND ALIENS
AND THEN I WENT
UP ON THE SHIP
AND SCOTT BAIO
GAVE ME PINK EYE.
THAT WASN'T
A DREAM, CARTMAN.
THAT REALLY HAPPENED.
OH, RIGHT.
WHY DON'T I HAVE
PINK EYE THEN ?
CARTMAN, YOU
DO HAVE PINK EYE.
SON-OF-A-BITCH !